

# **Anas Abdur Rohim**

 ■ anas.abdrohim@gmail.com

**L** +62 822-4586-1314

in anasabdur

anasark

anasabdur.com

## **About Me**

Web Developer with 5+ years of experience creating and maintaining websites and web applications in the information technology and services industry. As a confident and hardworking individual, will be committed to staying up-to-date with the latest web development trends and best practices, and continually improving my skills through self-study and professional development opportunities.

# Skills & Tools

Programming Language

: PHP, Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks

: Laravel, CodeIgniter, Vue.Js, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind

• Database Management

: MySql, MariaDb, Redis

• Other/Knowledge

: Docker, Git, Jenkins, RabbitMQ, Elasticsearch, Kibana,

Google Pub/Sub, Swagger, Server

# **Education**

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Maulana Malik Ibrahim State Islamic University

2013 - 2018 Malang, Indonesia

# Experience

**Full-Stack Developer** 

Niagahoster

Mar 2019 - Aug 2023 Yogyakarta, Indonesia

- Write clean code and functions and ensure security
- Collaborate with other teams to develop new features
- Create Rest APIs and integrate third parties
- · Test, maintenance, troubleshoot and debug issues
- Migration System

Web Developer

Feb 2018 - Jan 2019 Malang, Indonesia

PT. Spora Optima Global

- Design and develop websites
- Maintenance and optimization
- · Troubleshoot and fix bugs

Web Developer (Internship)

• Develop new features

PT. PLN (Persero)

Dec 2015 - Jan 2016 Malang, Indonesia

- Fix bug issues

# **Achievement**

- Best Team Member Of Engineering Q3 2020
- Best Team Member Of Engineering Q2 2022

# **Project Portfolio**

#### Niagahoster

- Maintenance existing features
- Development new features
- Maintenance and development landing pages
- Optimize performance, user experience, and SEO
- Troubleshoot and debug issues
- Connect the system with Third Parties
- Development Rest Api
- Migration system

#### Add Features for e-ujian.id

- Develop public bank soal (other schools can see the quiz and clone)
- Added CPNS types for exams
- Develop dynamic backgrounds for each school
- Implement Redis for exams
- Improve data reports
- Integrate with e-absensi

This system use CodeIgniter.

#### Web Application for e-absensi (e-ujian.id)

Develop a website application for student attendance using Laravel and integrate with e-ujian.id.

#### Add Features for client.morclinic.id

- Develop a referral feature in backend
- Develop a referral feature in frontend
- Create API Documentation

This system use Laravel and Vue.Js.

#### Add Features for Point.RED

- Develop a delivery note features (create, show, edit, approval, export, delete, email, print, history)
- Improve filter sales visitation
- Create API Documentation
- Write Unit Test

This system is microservices, front end use Vue.Js and backend use Laravel and Node.Js.

# Web Application for Ratson Inventory (ratson.com)

- Develop a master product feature
- Develop a purchase order feature
- Develop a inventory feature for stock
- Develop a report
- Improve user with 3 roles (owner, admin, staff)

This system use Laravel.

### Web Application for supercaderization.com

Develop a simple job portal web application systems for recruiters and job seekers.

# Company Profile for pbh.pertanian.jatimprov.go.id

Develop a company profile using WordPress.

# Company Profile for isolasi.co.id

Develop a company profile using WordPress.

# Online Store for jualsouvenirkatolik.com

Develop a simple online store using WordPress and WooCommerce plugins.